Sidestory of
A Certain Magical
Index
Hmm?
Hey, doesn't that look bad?
ね　あれ　大丈夫かな
<Judgement>
一応  風紀委員に
Maybe we should inform the Judgment, just in case.
連絡しておくか
This city never fails to keep me entertained.
ほんと　退屈しないわね　この町は
2.3 million people live here in Academy City,
総人口230万人
その実に八割を学生がしめる町
and 80% of them are students.
Prospective Students Academy City Visit
それがこの学院都市です
You could call this city a huge experiment. All of the technology here is cutting edge.
科学技術の最先端が集まった　いわば巨大な一つ実験都市
学院としたそれ以外では
In fact, this city is apparently around 20 or 30 years more technologically advanced than the outside world.
使用される技術に20年から30年の開きがあると言われています
So... what are you going to study here?
そして　ここで皆がお勉強するのは？
超能力
Superhuman powers!
I want to be a Precog.
大切なお子様をお預かりするのに
The Academy City employs the finest in security measures to keep your children safe.
学院都市は万全の治安体制を布いています
どうぞご安心
Rest assured that-
いったたたた
Ouch...
What was that?
何なの？一体何が
What happened?
The traffic lights are...
信号が
ちょっと
Damn!
くそう　ついてね
How unlucky!
Just what is she?
一体何なんだあいつは
お待ちなさいな
Please wait up.
<Judgement>
風紀委員です
I'm from Judgment.
いったたたた
Owowowowowouch!
You must be that hoodlum that I've been summoned for.
通報にあった暴漢と言うのはあなたですわね
くそ
Damn it.
This is Shirai Kuroko. I have captured one of the suspects.
こちら白井黒子　犯人の一人を確保
初春　残りの野蛮人どもはどこですの
Uiharu, where are the other savages?
その路地の突き当りをひたりへ　５メートル先をさらにひたりです
Go left at the end of the alley.
Head straight for five meters, then take another left.
了解ですの
Understood!
<Judgement>
風紀委員ですの
I am a member of Judgment, coming in response to a call.
通報を受けて参りました
どうぞ大人しくお縄に
Resistance is futile, allow us to take you under-
ん　これって
What the...
お　黒子
Oh, Kuroko?
Onee-sama?!
お姉様！
放て！心に刻んだ夢を
未来さえ置き去りにして
限界など知らない　意味無い！
この能力が光散らす　その先に遥かな想いを
チカラ
歩いてきた　この道を　振り返ることしか
出来ないなら…今ここで全てを壊せる
暗闇に堕ちる街並み
人はどこまで立ち向かえるの？
加速するその痛みから
誰かをきっと守れるよ
Looking! The blitz loop this planet to search way.
Only my RAILGUN can shoot it. 今すぐ
身体中を　光の速さで　駆け巡った　確かな予感
掴め！望むものなら残さず　輝ける自分らしさで
信じてるよ　あの日の誓いを
この瞳に光る涙　それさえも強さになるから
Sheesh, how many times do I have to tell you?
全く！何度申し上げたら分かっていただけますの？
It's our task as Judgements to preserve order in Academy City!
<Judgement>
学院都市の治安維持は私たち風紀委員のお仕事ですのよ
We can't have you picking fights like this.
勝手に立ち回られては困りますわ
Are you listening to me, Onee-sama?
聞いていますのお姉様！
Well, sorry. You'll just have to deal with it, since I finished them up before you got there.
だからしょうがないでしょう
あんたたちが来る前に終わちゃうんだから
If students get violent without authorization...
権限のない学生が暴れると
The authorities won't be happy.
お上に睨まれますわよ
Then you should have arrived at the scene sooner.
だったらもっと早く駆けつけることね
Seriously, this Academy City totally fails to live up to its name.
大体学院都市も名前負けなのよ
They might have tons of security systems everywhere, but idiots like those guys keep appearing.
町中にセキュリティ張り巡らせても
あの手のバカは絶滅しなし
I mean, they say the technology is so great and all, but...
最先端科学だ何だと謳っても
Onee...
お姉　え？
FAILURE!
Chest
It doesn't affect our lives in the slightest.
ほとんど私達の生活には関係ないじゃん
Onee-sama, why must you persist in wearing such tacky clothing under your skirt?
お姉様ったら
まだスカートの下にそんな無粋なおめしもの
What the hell are you looking at?
どこ見てんのよ！
I can move more freely if I wear this, and-
このほうが動きやしくてあたた
Failure detected in vending machine 7115.
自動販売機7116号
不具合確認
Suspected vandalism...
器物損害の疑いがあります　器物損害の疑いがあります
Please think twice before acting so hastily.
軽率な行動はおつつしみあそばせん？
Ah, we've gotta hurry!
あらいけない　急ぎませんと
<System Scan>
そうか　今日は身体検査の日だっけ
Oh, right, we've got a system scan today.
7th Academy Block Public Announcement:
Body scans for students in the following schools will take place today:
Tokiwadai Junior High
Sakugawa Junior High
Asahi Junior High
Tokiwadai Private Junior Highschool
Schedule for today's body scan:
Telekinetic types
11:00~  School grounds
Psykokinetic types
11:00~   Classroom building 1, Classroom 42
Perceptive types
11:00~  Classroom 1
Mindreading  Classroom 37
Precog   Classroom26
Sight types
11:00~ Classroom buidling 1
Farsight   Classroom 37
Seethrough Classroom 26
Wave.
波
Star.
星
Wave.
波
Circle.
丸
Do 38 degrees next.
次　38度
Yes ma'am.
はい
You are off by 0.2mm
誤差0.2ミリ
Okay, you're finished.
結構です　では　次の方
Next person, please?
The record is 78 meters and 23 centimeters.
記録78メートル23センチ
You were off from the specified mark by 54cm.
指定位置との誤差54センチ
Your overall evaluation is Level 4.
<Level 4>
総合評価 大能力者
Geez, I'm not performing at my best...
調子が今一つですの
Must be because of that Judgment job yesterday...
<Judgement>
やっぱりき昨日の風紀委員の仕事が影響して
You have a bleak future ahead of you if you have to rely on excuses like that, Shirai Kuroko-san.
そんな言い訳なさるようでは　先は見えてますわね　白井黒子さん
Kongo Mitsuko...
婚後光子
I'll reach Level 5 before you at this rate.
<Level 5>
この分だと　　超能力者に到達するのは
私のほうが先かしら
Don't compare your ability with mine.
私とあなたの能力を一緒にしてほしくはありませんの
The methods of spacial recognition used for the third and eleventh dimensions are completely different...
大体三次元と十一次元では空間把握法が本番的に
You know, I've never liked you to begin with. You're awfully arrogant for a first year.
もともと私一年の凡才で大きな顔をするあなたが気に入りませんの
Understand?
よろしくて　この私常盤台のエースとなったに暁に　　あ！
You just don't listen, do you?
相変わらす人の話を聞きやがりません
When I become the ace of Tokiwadai...
What was that?
An explosion?
何事ですの？
Maybe you don't know about it, since you just transferred in this year, but...
本年度から二年に転入してきたあなたはご存知ないかもしれませんが
Tokiwadai's ace is having her ability checked in the pool right now.
今あのプールで能力測定されているのが　常盤台のエースですわ
She has so much destructive power that they need to use the pool water as a shock absorbant.
プールの水を緩衝材にしなければ
まともに計測もできないほどの破壊力
Do you think you can take that blast directly?
あの一撃を真正面から受ける覚悟があなたにあって？
The record for initial shell speed is 1300 meters per second.
記録　砲弾初速
予測1030メートル
Firing rate, 8 shots per minute.
連発能力　毎分八発
Hit distribution, 18.9mm.
着弾分布18.9ミリ
Your overall evaluation is Level 5.
<Level 5>
総合評価　超能力者
Oh, you could hear it all the way from the grounds?
え？校庭まで音届いてたの？
It was such a huge blast.
すごい音でしたもの
Everyone was really surprised.
みんな驚いていましたわ
Man, they can't even measure my ability properly without resorting to this...
全く　あんな方法じゃないとまともに測点もできないなんて
You have a much more useful ability than I do.
私のより黒子の能力のほうがよっぽど便利でいいわ
The grass looks greener on the other side of the fence.
隣のしばふは青く見えるんですのよ
Well... you may have a point there... but still.
そりゃまあそうかもしれないけど
You're the ace of Tokiwadai, no matter what anyone says.
なんといっても
お姉様は常盤台のエース
So you can hold your chest out with pride.
堂々と胸を張っていればよいのですわ
Ace, eh...
エースで
But, well...
まあ　もっとも
Though... these breasts are a bit too small to stand out on their own.
張ると言うには　自己主張の足りないつつましい胸ですけど
Your modesty is your sin, Onee-sama
ああ でもこのつつましさこそがお姉様の罪深さ
Oh, you tempt me so gracefully, and yet enchantingly... My heart is about to break!
奥ゆかしくも悩まし誘惑に
黒子は　黒子の心は
壊れてしまいそう
You're already broken!
いやなんから壊れてるよあんたは！
I just wanted some intimacy!
ただのスキンシップですのに
Shut up!
うるさい！
Seventh Academic Block
Hmm.
ええと
Uiharun~.
う～い～は～る
Ah, pink with polka dots today.
今日は淡いピンクの水玉か
きゃあああ
What are you doing to me, Saten-san!?
いきなり何するんですか！佐天さん
ああ　クラスメートに敬語とは　相変わらず他人行儀だね
Come on, you don't need to be so polite with me. We're classmates, right?
Perhaps I should do it again to strengthen our bonds?
どれ　親睦を深かめるためにもう一回
You're so mean...
ひどいですよ
Sorry, sorry, I went too far.
ごめんごめん　調子に乗っちゃって
Wanna see mine instead?
代わりにあたしのパンツみる？
No way.
結構です　もう佐天さんは
Geez, Saten-san.
Oh, so how'd it go?
そういやどうだった？
How'd what go?
どうって？
The system scan, of course.
決まってるじゃん
<System Scan>
身体検査
おお　全然ダメでした
It went terribly.
I got Level 1, as usual.
<Level 1>
相変わらずの低能力者
I haven't improved since elementary school.
小学校のころからずっと横ばいです
The teacher in charge of me even told me this:
担当の先生からも　お前の頭の花は見せ掛けか
"Are the flowers on your head just for decoration?"
"Those are flowers in full bloom, so your ability level should be too!"
その花の満開パワーで能力試験も咲き誇れって
Umm, I'm not really sure if that's the right method of encouragement, but anyway...
ええと　その担当の説教にもいろいろ突っ込みたいところだけど
You should cheer up a bit.
まあ　とりあえず　元気出しなよ
I mean, at least you're Level 1.
<Level 1>
大体低能力者なら
まだいいじゃん
I'm a Level 0. An Abilityless.
あたしなんてLevel 0
無能力者だよ
But I don't mind it.
でもそんなのは気にしない
As long as everything's fun, I don't care.
あたしは毎日が楽しければ　それでオッケー
Saten-san...
佐天さん
Come on, listen to this and cheer up.
ほら　これ聞いて元気出しな
Oh, it's Hitotsui Hajime...
あ　『ひとついはじめ』　これって？
This is...
I downloaded the pre-release of this track while they were streaming it.
先行配信されたの曲をダウンロードしたの
The album with it is going on sale today.
今日この曲が入ってるアルバムの発売日なんだ
You're gonna buy the CD after downloading it?
ダウンロードしたのにＣＤも買うんですか？
You can't call yourself a true fan unless you receive Premium Goods from the lottery by buying the limited
初回限定場の応募券で抽選100名にあたるプレミアムグッツをゲットしてこそ
first edition release as one of 100 lucky winners.
真のファンと言うもんでしょうか
I see...
あ
So we're gonna go buy it together!
という訳で一緒に買いに行くよ
Um, I have plans with Shirai-san today.
でも私今日は白井さんと約束が
By Shirai-san, you mean Shirai Kuroko, the member of Judgment?
<Judgement>
白井さんって　風紀委員の白井黒子？
She's finally gonna let me meet Misaka-san! I've begged her so much!
願叶え 御坂さんに見合せってもらえることになったんです
Misaka Mikoto-san, the ace of Tokiwadai and one of the only Level 5s in the city!
<Level 5>
学院都市でも七人しかいない超能力者
I'm gonna get to meet her!
常盤台のエース　御坂美琴さんに
A Level 5 from Tokiwadai?
<Level 5>
常盤台の超能力者?
Isn't she just another one of those whores who look down on everyone else and think their own ability is all that?
どうせまた能力をかさにきた上から目線でいけすかない奴じゃないの
She's not like that...
そんなこと
All of them laugh at people with crappier abilities.
だってああいう人たちって
自分よりしたの人間を小ばかにするじゃん
They're so annoying.
むかつくんだよね
And she's an ojou-sama from Tokiwadai, right?
しかも常盤台のお嬢さまだなんで
No, ojou-sama is the best!
いいんじゃないですか　お嬢さま
She's the best because she's an ojou-sama!
いいえ　むしろお嬢様だからいいんじゃないですか
Man, you're one of those people who think celebrities are great just because they're famous.
ってあんた　単にセレブな人種に憧れてるだけなんじゃ
N-not at all.
そ　そんなことないですよ
By the way, I'm from Nishikasai, so that has nothing to do with it.
ちなみに私の出身が西葛西だってことも関係ないですよ
You should come along too. This is a great chance.
そうだ　この際だから佐天さんも一緒に
But I'm not...
あたしは別に
Don't worry.
大丈夫大丈夫
Don't worry about what?
大丈夫って　ちょっ
H-Hey...
You don't get a chance like this every day!
そんな機会めったにないですよ
Wait, Uiharu!
ちょっとまで　初春
#1 Electromaster
A Certain Scientific Railgun
A fan of mine?
私のファン？
Yeah, a girl who's been serving as my backup in squad 177 of Judgment.
風紀委員の第177支部で私のバックハップを担当してくれている子ですの
She keeps telling me about how much she wants to meet you.
一度でいいからお姉様にお会いしたいと事あるごとに
ああ
Now, I know you find the actions of your fangirls disgusting, but...
お姉様が常日頃からファンの子達の無礼な振る舞いに閉口されているのは存じてますわ
Uiharu is a nice, polite girl.
けれど初春は本別をわきまえた大人しい子
Furthermore, she's one of the few people I would consider my friend.
それに何より　私が認めた数少ない友人　ここは黒子に免じて一つ
So, please, for my sake...
Oh, of course. In order to keep your stress level to a minimum, I've prepared the perfect schedule for today-
もちろん　お姉様のストレスを最小限におさえるべく
今日の予定は私がばっちり
Oh!
あ　ちょっ
Hey!
Hmm?
何々～初春を口実にしたお姉様とのデートプラン
"My plans for a date with Onee-sama, using Uiharu as an excuse."
"Part 1: Go to a restaurant to strengthen our friendship."
其の一　ファミレスで親睦を深め
"Part 2: Go to the lingerie shop (to buy sexy underwear)"
其の二ランジェリショップ（決勝下着購入）
"Part 3: Go shopping at the perfume store (to buy aphrodisiacs)"
其の三アロマショップでショッピング（媚薬購入）
"Part 4: Delete Uiharu"
其の四初春駆除
"Part 5: Go to a love hotel with Onee-sama."
其の五お姉様とホテルへ行こう
So, in other words, you're going to take advantage of your nice, polite friend in order to live out your sick fantasies.
つまり大人しくて本別ある友人を利用して
自分の変態願望叶えようと
読んでるだけで
My stress level is shooting through the roof just reading this!
すっげストレスたまるんだけど！
But, well...
まあでも　黒子の友達じゃん　しょうがないか
I guess I'll have to go along with it, if she's a friend of yours...
Onee-sama!
お姉様
Hey, Kuroko!
I didn't know you loved me so much!
あ！黒っ
お姉様がそんなにも黒子のことを思ってくださったなんて
I'm going to... I'm going crazy!
黒子はもう　もうどうにかなってしまいそう！お姉様！
Miss...
お客さん　　申し訳ありませんが
Onee-sama!
I'm sorry, but you're disturbing the other customers...
ほかにお客様のお迷惑になりますので
Well, then,
と言う訳でとりあえずご紹介しますわ
please allow me to introduce you.
This is Uiharu Kazari-san, a first year at Sakugawa middle school.
こちら柵川中学一年　初春飾利さんですの
N-Nice to meet you.
は　初めまして　初春飾利です
I'm Uiharu Kazari.
And this is...
それから
Cheers. I'm Saten Ruiko, Uiharu's classmate.
どうも　初春のクラスメートの佐天涙子です
I dunno why, but I'm tagging along.
何だが知らないけど　ついてきちゃいましだ
By the way, I'm a Level 0.
<Level 0>
ちなみに能力値は無能力です
ああ　佐天さん何を
S-Saten-san, why are you telling her that?
Uiharu-san and Saten-san...
初春さんに佐天さん　私は御坂美琴　よろしく
I'm Misaka Mikoto.
Nice to meet you.
N-Nice to...
ん　よろしく
...meet you.
お願いします
Well, since the introduction's gone off without a hitch...
では恙無い紹介も済んだところで　多少予定はくるってしまいましたが
I have a schedule for today planned,
so, even though it's been thrown a bit out of whack-
今日の予定はこの黒子がぱっち
Ouch...
痛い
全く
Well... No point in staying here,
まあ　こんなところにいっても仕方ないし
so why don't we go to the arcade?
とりあえず　ゲーセンへ行こうか
Eh?
Arcade, eh?
ゲーセン ですか
Hey, Kuroko, let's go.
ほら　黒子行くよ
Geez, Onee-sama.
もう　お姉様ったら　ゲームとか立ち読みではなく
You should take up a hobby that suits you more.
You know, like flower arrangement or playing the koto,
もっとこうお花とかお琴とか
not playing video games or reading manga.
ご自身にふさわしいご趣味をお持ちになれませんの
Shut up.
うるさいわね
Just what makes you think those would suit me?
大体お茶やお琴のどこが私らしいっていうのよ！
She doesn't act like an ojou-sama at all, does she?
なんかさ　全然お嬢様じゃなくない
She doesn't look down at us, either.
上から目線でもないですね
Oh, what is that?
何それ
Rablun - 7th Academic Block - Fureai Plaza
Newly Opened!!
To the first 100 customers: Free Gift "Gekota (gentleman version)"!
Looks like it's a new crepe shop.
新しいクレープ屋さん見たいですね
It says they'll give a Gekota doll to the first 100 customers.
先着100名様にゲコ太マスコットプレゼントって
That's a pretty crappy mascot...
何だこの安いキャラ
Come on, nobody's gonna fall for this nowadays-
今時こんなのに食いつく人なんて
Oh, pardon me.
あ　すみま
Misaka-san?
御坂さん
What's the matter, Onee-sama?
どうなさいましたの？お姉様
Oh, does the crepe shop interest you?
あら～クレープ屋さんにご興味が
Or perhaps it's that free gift that interests you?
それとも　もれなくもらえるプレゼントのほうですの
な　何言ってんのよ
W-What are you talking about?
I-I'm not interested in that Gekota thing at all!
わ　私は別にゲコ太なんか
Look, it's a frog. It's an amphibian.
ふん　だって　蛙よ　両生類よ！
There's no such thing as a girl who would want that...
どこの世界にこんなものもらって喜ぶ女の子がい
Oh...
Oh wow, there are a ton of people here.
わ～すごい人
Why are there so many kids?
なんてこんなにちっちゃい子が
We're taking a one hour break.
休憩は一時間です
Please don't wander too far.
あんまり遠くに行かないでくださいね
Bad timing, huh.
タイミングが悪かったみたいですね
I'll go secure a bench.
先にベンチを確保してまいりますわ
Oh, I'll come too.
じゃ　私も
Please order for us, Saten-san.
佐天さん　私たちの分をお願いしますね
I'll pay up later.
お金は後でお支払いしますわ
H-Hey...
ちょっ
Oh, what?
え？なに？
Nothing...
いいえ　あの　順番変わります？
Err...
Should we change places?
I-I don't care where I am in line.
別に順番なんて　私はクレープさえ買えたらこれでいい
As long as I can buy the crepe...
Woohoo! I got a Gekota!
やった～ゲットゲット
Me too!
私も私も
Sorry to keep you waiting.
お待たせしました
Here you are.
はい　どうぞ
This is the last one.
最後の一個ですよ
Thank you.
どうも
Wait, what? The last one?
え　最後？
Umm...
あ　あの　よかったらこれ
You can have this, if you really want it...
Really? You'll let me have it?
いいの？ 本当にいいの？
S-Sure...
ええ
THANK YOU!
ありがとう
You're welcome...
い　いいえ
Now, now, Onee-sama.
ほらお姉様　遠慮なさらず
Don't be so shy.
I told you already! I don't want it!
いらないって言ってんでしょう
Why exactly would you choose a combination of natto and cream as your topping?
何をトッピングに納豆と生クリームで
ほらほら　あ
I told you to quit it!
やめなさい
It was nice.
よかったですね
Hmm?
ん？
Misaka-san is a lot friendlier than I imagined,
御坂さん
お嬢様のイメージとはちょっと違ったけど
even though she doesn't really match my image of an ojou-sama.
思ってたよりずっと親しみやすい人で
I wonder...
どうなんだかね
Here.
はい
Here?
はい？
You want to try some, right?
味見でしょう
I'd like to thank you for back then.
先のお礼　一口どうぞ
Please take a bite.
Eh...
え
Onee-sama!
お姉様！お姉様は私というものありながら
Onee-sama, you have me... You'd rather share an indirect kiss with Saten-san than with me!?
さ　佐天さんとの間接キッス
I can't keep up with your friend over here.
あんたの友たちにはついていけないかも
Oh?
Hmm?
ん？
That's the bank over there.
いえ　あそこの銀行何ですけど
Why do they have the anti-burglary shutters drawn during the daytime?
なんで昼間から防犯シャッター下ろしてるんでしょうか
Huh?
W-What was that?
何なの
Uiharu, report to the Antiskills and see if we've suffered any casualties.
<Antiskill>
初春　警備員への連絡と
怪我人無有の確認
Hurry up!
急いでくださいな
はい
Kuroko!
黒子
That's a no.
いけませんわお姉様
It's Judgment's job to maintain order in the Academy City.
<Judgement>
学院都市の治安維持は私たち風紀委員のお仕事
Can you behave yourself this time?
今度こそ　お行儀よくしていってくださいな
Yes, that's right.
はい　そうです
There's a robbery at the bank in Fureai Plaza in the 7th Academy Block.
第七学院ふれあい広場前の銀行で
<Antiskill>
強盗事件発生　警備員の出動要請します
We're asking for a deployment of Antiskill troops.
Don't mess around!
ほら　ぐつぐつすんな　さっさとしねいと
We have to hurry, or else...
Wait up, please.
お待ちなさい
I'm Judgment.
<Judgement>
風紀委員ですの
You're under arrest in act for robbery and destruction of personal property.
器物破損　及び強盗の現行犯で　拘束します
Hmm...
Hmm?
Who is this brat?
何だこのガキ
Judgment needs to hire better people!
ジャッジメントも人手不足か
Hey, girl. You'd better get out of our way...
おらお嬢じゃん
とっとどっかいかないと
Unless you wanna get hurt!
怪我しちゃうぜ
When wimps like you say stuff like that...
そういう三下のせりふは
Well, it's a death flag.
死亡フラグですわよ
Wha-?
Damn you!
てめぇ
Amazing!
すごい
Nice work, Kuroko.
さすが黒子
You can't!
ダメですって
You mustn't leave the plaza now!
今広場から出たら
But...!
でも
What's the matter?
どうしたの？
Well...
それが
A boy is missing!
男の子が一人足りないです
He said he forgot something on the bus a few minutes ago,
少し前にバスに忘れ物したって言ったきり
and he's been missing ever since!
Okay, Uiharu-san and I will look for him.
じゃ　私と初春さんで
I'm going too!
私も行きます
All right.
分かった
Let's split up and search.
手分けして探しましょう
You're out of time for regrets!
いまさら後悔しても遅せぞ
Since you've made me get serious...
A Pyrokinetic?
<Pyrokinesist>
発火能力者
本気にさせたらには　てめには消し炭に
Geez.
Prepare to become ash.
ったく
Hey...
おい　厄介よ
Did you think you could escape?
Who's gonna-
誰が
She disappeared!?
消えた
escape?
逃げますの
A-A Teleporter?
<Teleporter>
空間移動能力者
If you resist further, I'll teleport this right into your body.
これ以上抵抗するなら
<Teleport>
次はこれを体内に直接空間移動させますわよ
How's it going over there?
そっちは？
Not good.
ダメです
Where did he go, man?
どっこ行ったのよ　もう
Hey, what are you doing?
あ　何だお前
Ah, I can use you.
ちょうどいい
Come with me.
一緒に来い
What are you doing, onii-chan?
何？お兄じゃん？誰？
Who are you?
Just come with me!
いいから来いって　早く
Hurry up!
I can too!
あたしだって
We should go search the plaza again-
やっぱり広場のほうもう一度さが
Who are you?
何だてめぇ　離せよ
Let go!
Huh?
No!
ダメ
Damn!
くそ
Saten-san!
佐天さん
Kuroko!
黒子
Eh?
Looks like things just got personal.
こっからは私の個人的な喧嘩だから
Sorry, but you'll have to deal with the interference.
悪いけど
手　出させてもらうわよ
I remember now.
思い出した
Judgment has this Teleporter with a really nasty reputation...
<Judgement>
風紀委員にほ
捕まったが最後
You're done for if she catches you. She'll shred your body and your soul to pieces.
<Teleporter>
身も心も踏みにじって最後無能にする最悪の空間移動能力者がいって
Who are you talking about?
誰のことですのそれ
Damn it!
ちくしょう　このまま引き下がれけよ
I can't just back out of this!
Furthermore, there's an Electromaster who reigns over said Teleporter's own body and soul.
<Teleporter>
更に　その空間移動能力者の身も心もとりこりする
<Electro Master>
最強の電撃使いが
I'll take care of you...
こなっや　てめぇらまとめて
Yes, and she is...
そう　あの方こそが
At the top of that 2.3 million.
学院都市に230万人の頂点
The third of the seven Level 5s.
<Level 5>
七人の超能力者の第三位
Railgun.
<Railgun>
超電磁砲
Misaka Mikoto-oneesama.
御坂美琴お姉様
Tokiwadai middle school's pride. Our invincible Electric Princess.
常盤台中学が誇る
最強無敵な電撃姫ですの
A-
す
Amazing...
すごい
No civilians were injured!
一般の方の負傷者はセローです　それと
And...
P-Please walk quickly.
さ…さっさと歩いてください
Your power was quite something.
あなたの能力もなかなかのものでしたわよ
I would estimate it to be around Level 3.
<Level 3>
強能力と
いったところかしら
Looks like you got too cocky about your ability and started walking down the wrong path.
能力に有頂天になるあまり
道を違いたようですわね
Reflect on what you've done and choose the correct path once more.
しばらく自分を見つめなおして
もう一度手直してくださいな
Thank you so much!
本当にありがとうございました
No I...
いいえ　あの
I don't know how to thank you.
何とお礼をいっていいか　ほら　あなたも
No, you too.
Thank you, onee-chan!
お姉ちゃん　ありがとう
Nice work, Saten-san.
お手柄立ったね　佐天さん
え？
You were really cool.
すごく格好よかったよ
You were, too.
御坂さんも
Onee-sama!
お姉様
Hey, Kuroko!
Saten-san, are you doing okay?
佐天さん　お怪我　大丈夫ですか
I'm just fine.
平気平気
Really?
本当ですか
Misaka-san was so cool!
やめなさい
御坂さんもすごく格好よかったです
That's enough!
いい加減にしろ
Dear My Friend Every day & night
Always be with you
Dear My Friend every day & night
話しても　まだまだ　足りないまま
夕焼けが　街を染めてゆく
思うように　なかなか　いかない…って
気づいたら　一緒に　泣いていた
恋も　夢も　花も　虹も　風も
ぜんぶ掴もうよ
ダイジョウブ！　元気出して
私がそばにいるから
今日のミス　悔やむより　今　乗り越えて
ダイジョウブ！　迷わないで
まだ見ぬ未来へと向かって
ずっと　歩いてゆこう
Dear My Friend every day & night
Always be with you
That Misaka-san of mine was really something!
Next Episode
憧れの御坂さん素敵でした
You need to stay
hydrated if you
work under the sun
Yeah, really.
本当だねえ
Hey, Saten-san!
佐天さん　私の頭に水かけないでください
Don't pour water on my head!
But your flowers will die!
だって　お花が枯れちゃうちゃん
来週も熱くなるんってよ
I hear it's gonna be hot again next week.